Guide to the New-York Historical Society Portrait Collection, circa 1640-2020 (bulk, 1800-1950) PR 52
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Individuals and Family Groups
  - Subseries I.B. Individuals and Family Groups: Medium Format
    - Carter, James C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cartier, Jacques (Drawer Medium)
    - Casey, Silas (Drawer Medium)
    - Cass, Lewis (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Cassin, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Castro, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Casy, Phoebe (Drawer Medium)
    - Catlin, Marcus (Drawer Medium)
    - Catron, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Caule, H. L. W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cecilia, St. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cenci, Beatrice (Drawer Medium)
    - Cellini, Benvenuto (Drawer Medium)
    - Cervera, Pasqual (Drawer Medium)
    - Chace, William M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Chalmers, J. R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Chamberlain, J. L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Chamberlain, V. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Chambliss, James R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Champaigne, Philippe de (Drawer Medium)
    - Champlain, Samuel de (Drawer Medium)
    - Chanler, Margaret (Drawer Medium)
    - Chapin, E.H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Chaplin, Ch. (Drawer Medium)
    - Chapman, George H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Chapman, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Chappell, William CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Charlick, Oliver (Drawer Medium)
    - Charcot, Jean Martin (Drawer Medium)
    - Chase, Philander (Drawer Medium)
    - Chase, Salmon P. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Chase, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Chauncy, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Cheatham, B. F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cheever, George B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Chelmsford, Frederic John Napier Thesiger, Viscount (Drawer Medium)
    - Cheselden, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Chesnut, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Chew, Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - Child, Daniel Lee (Drawer Medium)
    - Childs, Cephas C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Childs, George W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Chittenden, Simeon Baldwin [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Chittenden, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Choate, Rufus (Drawer Medium)
    - Chollar, Byron Edgar (Drawer Medium)
    - Christiancy, J. P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Church, George E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Church, Sanford E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Churchill, T. J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cinquez, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Cipriani, Giovan Battista (Drawer Medium)
    - Clark, Aaron C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Clark, Abra (Drawer Medium)
    - Clark, Charles E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Clark, Emmons (Drawer Medium)
    - Clark, Frances (Drawer Medium)
    - Clark, George H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Clark, Luther (Drawer Medium)
    - Clark, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Clark, Willis G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Clarkson, Matthew (Drawer Medium)
    - Clarkson, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Clausen, George Caspar (Drawer Medium)
    - Clay, Cassius M. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Clay, Clemont C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Clay, Henry (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Clay, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Clayton, Powell (Drawer Medium)
    - Cleburne, P. R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Clerke, William B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cleveland, Grover (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Individual, and with Frances Folsom Cleveland
      Scenes from his life
      ....Inauguration
      ....General
    - Clifford, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Clifford, Nathan (Drawer Medium)
    - Clingman. T. L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Clinton, A. J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Clinton, Anne Floyd (Drawer Medium)
    - Clinton, George (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Clinton, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Clinton, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Cluseret, Gustave (Drawer Medium)
    - Clushing (Drawer Medium)
    - Clymer, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Coates, Lindley (Drawer Medium)
    - Coates, Alice L. Canoune (Drawer Medium)
    - Coatsworth, George, Mrs. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cobb, Frank (Drawer Medium)
    - Cobb, Howell (Drawer Medium)
    - Cobb, Howell, Mrs. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cobb, T. R. R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cobbett, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Cobden, Richard (Drawer Medium)
    - Coburn, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Cochran, Fanny Travis (Drawer Medium)
    - Cochran, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Cochrane, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Cockrell, Francis Marion (Drawer Medium)
    - Coe, Jonathan, Jr. (Drawer Medium)
    - Coe, William G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Coffin, Charles Carleton (Drawer Medium)
    - Coggeshall, Edwin W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cogswell, Cornelia McClure (tombstone) (Drawer Medium)
    - Colden, Cadwallader (Drawer Medium)
    - Colden, Cadwallader D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Colden, David C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cole, Abraham (Drawer Medium)
    - Cole, M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cole, Wm. A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Coleman, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Colfax, Schuyler (Drawer Medium)
    - Colgate, Jas. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Colgate, Robert [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Colgate, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Colles, Christopher (Drawer Medium)
    - Collins, N. G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Colston, A. E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Colt, Henrietta L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Columbus, Christopher (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Coman, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Comstock, Samuel Willett (Drawer Medium)
    - Conairde, George W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Conard, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Condit, J. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cone, T. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cones, Samuel E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Conner, D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Conner, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Conness, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Connor, Rowland CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Conrad, Robert Taylor (Drawer Medium)
    - Conyngham, D. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Constant, Jean Joseph Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - Coolidge, Calvin (Drawer Medium)
    - Cook, Eliza (Drawer Medium)
    - Cook, Philip (Drawer Medium)
    - Cooke, Jay (Drawer Medium)
    - Cooke, Philip George (Drawer Medium)
    - Cooper, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Cooper, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Cooper, James Fenimore (Drawer Medium)
    - Cooper, Peter (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Cooper, S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cooper, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Cooper, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Corbin, H. C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Corbino, Jon (New York artist) (Drawer Medium)
    - Corcoran, Michael (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Cornell, Alonzo B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cornett, Reba (Drawer Medium)
    - Cornish, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Cornwallis, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Corot, C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Correggio (Drawer Medium)
    - Corse, John M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Corse, M. D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Corwin, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Cosden, Alfred H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cotogniz, Antonio (Drawer Medium)
    - Cotter, Joseph B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cotton, Nathaniel (Drawer Medium)
    - Couch, Darius N. (Drawer Medium)
    - Courbet, Gustave (Drawer Medium)
    - Couture, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Cowan, Edgar (Drawer Medium)
    - Cowden, Elliot C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cowdin, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Cox (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Cox, J. Dolson
      Cox, James
      Cox, John Vache
      Cox, Mary Eliza
      Cox, Samuel S.
      Cox, William R.
    - Coxe, A. Cleveland [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Coxe, Daniel (Drawer Medium)
    - Craig, C. F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Crane (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Crane, John
      Crane, Sarah Briggs
    - Crawford, S. W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Crawford, T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Crawford, W. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Creeger, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Creighton, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Cresson, Elliott (Drawer Medium)
    - Crittenden, T. L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Crittenden, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Crocker, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Crocker, John S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Crocker, Marcellus M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Crockett, David (Drawer Medium)
    - Croker, Edward Franklin (Drawer Medium)
    - Crolius, Clarkson (Drawer Medium)
    - Croll, William Cuyler (Drawer Medium)
    - Cromwell, A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cromwell, Frederic (Drawer Medium)
    - Cromwell, Oliver (Drawer Medium)
    - Crosby, Frank Butler CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Cruger, S. van Rensselaer (Drawer Medium)
    - Cruger, S. van Rensselaer, Mrs. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cullen, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Cunningham, E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Curtis, Alfred A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Curtis, Benjamin Robbins (Drawer Medium)
    - Curtis, George William (Drawer Medium)
    - Curtis, Joseph B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Curtis, Samuel R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Curtiss, Cyrus [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Cushing, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Cushing, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Cushing, William Barker (Drawer Medium)
    - Custer, George A. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Cutler, L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cutter, Bloodgood H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cutting, F. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cutting, William Bayard (Drawer Medium)
    - Cuvier (Drawer Medium)
    - Cuyler, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Cuyler, Jonathan M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Cuyler, Theodore Ledyard (Drawer Medium)
    - Cuyp, Aelbert (Drawer Medium)
    - Dabney, Alfred Stackpole, undated (Drawer Medium)
    - DaCasta, Charles M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dada, Hattie A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Daguerre, Louis-Jacques-Mandé (Drawer Medium)
    - Dahlgren, John A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dale, Caroline Wells Healy (Drawer Medium)
    - Dallas, A. J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dallas, George Mifflin (Drawer Medium)
    - Daly, Charles Patrick (Drawer Medium)
    - Dana, Charles A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dana, James D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dana, Paul (Drawer Medium)
    - Daniel, Junius (Drawer Medium)
    - Daniel, Peter Vivian (Drawer Medium)
    - Daniels, George H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Danielsz, Henrik Hooft (Drawer Medium)
    - Darby, Phebe Ogden (Drawer Medium)
    - Darly, F. O. C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Darrow, Clarence (Drawer Medium)
    - Dashiell, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Daubigny, Charles Francois (Drawer Medium)
    - Daudet, Alphonse (Drawer Medium)
    - Daumier, H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Davidson, John W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Davies, Henry E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Davies, Thomas A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Davis (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Davis, Henry
      Davis, Henry Gassaway
      Davis, Jefferson (separate folder)
      Davis, John L.
      Davis, John W.
      Davis, Noah
      Davis, Noah, judge [crossed out]
      Davis, Robert C.
      Davis, W. W. H.
    - Davison, Darius (Drawer Medium)
    - Dawes, Charles Gates (Drawer Medium)
    - Dawes, Henry L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dawson, George F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dawson, Henry B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Day, Albert W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Day, Benjamin H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Day, H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Day, William R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dayton, Charles Willoughby (Drawer Medium)
    - Dayton, Jonathan (Drawer Medium)
    - Dayton, William L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Deane, Silas (Drawer Medium)
    - De Bethune, Maximilien (Drawer Medium)
    - De Bow, James Dunwoody Brownson (Drawer Medium)
    - Decatur, Stephen (Drawer Medium)
    - Decker, John (Drawer Medium)
    - De Forret, Theodore R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Degoutte, Jean (Drawer Medium)
    - De Groot, Adelaide Milton (Drawer Medium)
    - Delaney, John J. CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - De La Noy, Catherine Peters (Drawer Medium)
    - De la Roche, Paul (Drawer Medium)
    - Delevan, Edward C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Delmonico, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - De Long, George Washington (Drawer Medium)
    - Dennis, Frederic Shephard (Drawer Medium)
    - Dent, F. J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dent, John H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dentinger, W. E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Depew, Chauncey M. (Drawer Medium)
    - De Peyster, Frederic (Drawer Medium)
    - De Peyster, J. Watts (Drawer Medium)
    - De Peyster, Jacob Ashton CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - De Peyster, Johannis (Drawer Medium)
    - De Ronde, Lambertus (Drawer Medium)
    - De Villiers, Francois Coulon (Drawer Medium)
    - Devin, Thomas C. (Drawer Medium)
    - DeVoe, Thomas F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dewart, William T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dewey, George (2 separate folders) (Drawer Medium)
    - Dewey, Orville (Drawer Medium)
    - Dewey, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - De Witt, Ella Flagg (Drawer Medium)
    - De Witt, George Gosman (Drawer Medium)
    - De Witt, Theodore (Drawer Medium)
    - De Witt, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Diaz, Armando (Drawer Medium)
    - Diaz de la Pena, N. (Drawer Medium)
    - Di Cesnola, Louis P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dickerson, M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dickinson, Anna (Drawer Medium)
    - Dickinson, John D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dill, C. C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Diman, J. Hugh (Drawer Medium)
    - Dinwiddie, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Dix, John A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Doane, Oliver (Drawer Medium)
    - Dockery, Thomas P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dodge, William E. Sr. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Dodge, William E. Jr. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Dodgson, Campbell (Drawer Medium)
    - Donelson, A. J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dongan, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Donizetti, Gaetano (Drawer Medium)
    - Doremus, R. Ogden, Mrs. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dorr, T. W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Douglas, Stephen A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Douglass, Frederick (Drawer Medium)
    - Dour, Neal (Drawer Medium)
    - Downing, Angelina Billings (Drawer Medium)
    - Downing, David Lorenzo (Drawer Medium)
    - Downing, Jack (Drawer Medium)
    - Doxtater, Robert B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Drake, Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Drayton, Charlotte Augusta Astor (Drawer Medium)
    - Drisler, Henry [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Drummond (Drawer Medium)
    - Duane, William J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dubois, Gualterus (Drawer Medium)
    - Duche, Thomas Spence (Drawer Medium)
    - Duaz (Drawer Medium)
    - Duer, William Alexander (Drawer Medium)
    - Duffield, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Dunbar, Duncan (Drawer Medium)
    - Duncan, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Duncombe, Thomas Slingsby (Drawer Medium)
    - Dunlap, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Dunlap, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Dunsmore, John Ward (Drawer Medium)
    - Dupont, Jacques-Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Dupont, Samuel Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Dupuis, Pierre (Drawer Medium)
    - Duran, Carolus (Drawer Medium)
    - Durand, Asher (Drawer Medium)
    - Duryee, A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Duy, Albert (Drawer Medium)
    - Duyckinck, Evert A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Dvorak, Antonin (Drawer Medium)
    - Dwight, Dr. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Dwight, M. Everett CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Eames, Wilberforce (tombstone) (Drawer Medium)
    - Earle, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Eastburn, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Eastlake, Charles Locke (Drawer Medium)
    - Easton, Robert Thomas Brown (Drawer Medium)
    - Eaton, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Eatom, William W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Edelinck, Gerard (Drawer Medium)
    - Edson, Franklin (Drawer Medium)
    - Edwards, Jonathan (Drawer Medium)
    - Edwards (Judge) [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Eigenbrodt, Charles S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Elder, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Eliot, Charles W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Eliot, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Ellery, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Elliott, Robert B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Ellis, A. Van Horne (Drawer Medium)
    - Ellis, Daniel (Drawer Medium)
    - Ellis, Julius L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Elliston (Drawer Medium)
    - Ellsler, Fanny (Drawer Medium)
    - Ellsworth, Elmer E. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Ellsworth, Oliver (Drawer Medium)
    - Ely, Smith (Drawer Medium)
    - Emerson, Ralph Waldo (Drawer Medium)
    - Emmet, Thomas Addis (Drawer Medium)
    - Endicott, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Engel, Nicholas (Drawer Medium)
    - English, William H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Eno, Amos R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Enright, Richard E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Eon de Beaumont, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Erben, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Erskine, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Estlin, John Bishop (Drawer Medium)
    - Estrada Cabrera, Manuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Eugenie (Drawer Medium)
    - Evangeline (Drawer Medium)
    - Evans, Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - Evans, Robley D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Evans, William Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Evarts, William M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Everett, Edward (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Ewell, Richard S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Ewing, I. (Drawer Medium)
    - Fairbanks, Charles W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Fairbanks, Jason (Drawer Medium)
    - Fairfax, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Fairless, Benjamin F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Fairman, Gideon (Drawer Medium)
    - Falconer, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Faraday, Michael (Drawer Medium)
    - Farington, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Farnsworth, Amos (Drawer Medium)
    - Farnsworth, Edward J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Farnsworth, John F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Farnum, Charlotte Barbara (Drawer Medium)
    - Farragut, David Glasgow (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Farrar, Geraldine (Drawer Medium)
    - Faulkner, Charles Jason (Drawer Medium)
    - Faunce, Jonathan (Drawer Medium)
    - Feehan, P. A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Feltman, C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Ferguson, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Ferrero, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Ferris, Isaac (Drawer Medium)
    - Ferris, Thomas T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Fersen, Axel (Drawer Medium)
    - Fessenden, Thomas G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Fessenden, William Pitt (Drawer Medium)
    - Few, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Field (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Field, Benjamin H.
      Field, Charles W.
      Field, Cyrus W.
      Field, David Dudley
      Field, Kate
      Field, Stephen Johnson
    - Fillmore, Millard (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Findley, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Fink, Louis M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Fish, Hamilton (Drawer Medium)
    - Fish, Nicholas (Drawer Medium)
    - Fisher, J. Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Fisher, Miers (Drawer Medium)
    - Fisk, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Fisk, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Fitch, A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Fitzgerald, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Flack, Alonzo (Drawer Medium)
    - Flagg, James Montgomery (Drawer Medium)
    - Flower, Roswell P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Floyd, J. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Foch, Ferdinand (Drawer Medium)
    - Foley, John S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Folger, Charles J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Follen, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Follen, Eliza Lee (Drawer Medium)
    - Foot, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Foote, Andrew H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Force, Peter (Drawer Medium)
    - Forestier-Walker, Frederick W. E. F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Forney, John H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Forsyth, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Forrest, N. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Foss, Cyrus D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Foster, John G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Foster, R. G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Foster, Stephen Collins (Drawer Medium)
    - Fowler, Bancroft (Drawer Medium)
    - Fowler, Charles H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Fox, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Fox sisters (Drawer Medium)
    - Francis, Converse (Drawer Medium)
    - Francis, John W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Francis, Lydia Maria (Drawer Medium)
    - Franklin, Benjamin (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Fraser, Martha Willets Mott (Drawer Medium)
    - Fraser, Simon (Drawer Medium)
    - Freeman, Bernardus (Drawer Medium)
    - Frelinghuysen, Frederick T. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Frelinghuysen, Theodore (Drawer Medium)
    - Fremont, John Charles and Jessie (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - French, S. G. (Drawer Medium)
    - French, W. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Fromentin, Eugene (Drawer Medium)
    - Frost, Rufus S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Fry, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Frye, Alexis E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Frye, Elizabeth Catherine Lilienthal (Drawer Medium)
    - Fujiwara, Jose (Drawer Medium)
    - Fuller, Henry V. (Drawer Medium)
    - Fuller, John W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Fuller, Melville Weston (Drawer Medium)
    - Fuller, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Fuller, Zelotes (Drawer Medium)
    - Fulton, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Furman, Garrit (Drawer Medium)
    - Furness, William H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gabrilowitsch, Clara (Drawer Medium)
    - Gadsden, Chris (Drawer Medium)
    - Gage, Lyman J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gage, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Galloway, Chas. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gail, Samuel P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gaine, Hugh (Drawer Medium)
    - Gaines, Edmund Pendleton (Drawer Medium)
    - Gallagher, Nicholas A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gallatin (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Gallatin, Albert
      Gallatin, Albert Eugene
      Gallatin, Albert R.
      Gallatin, Gaspar
    - Gano, R.M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gano, Stephen (Drawer Medium)
    - Garasche, J. P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Garcia, Malibran (Drawer Medium)
    - Gardner, Franklin (Drawer Medium)
    - Gardner, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Garfield, James A., and family (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Garland, A. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Garland, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Garnett, Richard Brooke (Drawer Medium)
    - Garnett, Robert Seldon (Drawer Medium)
    - Garnier, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Garrett, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Garrett, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Garrison, Cornelius K. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Garrison, William Lloyd (Drawer Medium)
    - Gary, Martin Witherspoon (Drawer Medium)
    - Gates, Horatio (Drawer Medium)
    - Gauche, Edward E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gay, Elizabeth Neale (Drawer Medium)
    - Gaynor, William J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Geary, John W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gehring, Charles E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gelette (Drawer Medium)
    - Gerard, James Watson (Drawer Medium)
    - Gerhardus, Victor (Drawer Medium)
    - Gervais, John Lewis (Drawer Medium)
    - Getty, George W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Ghezzi, Pietro Leone (Drawer Medium)
    - Gibbons, A. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gibbons, J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gibbons, James, Cardinal (Drawer Medium)
    - Gibbs, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Gibbs, R. P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gilbert de Voisins (Drawer Medium)
    - Gibert, William Nicholas (Drawer Medium)
    - Gibson, R. L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Giddings, Joshua R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Giles, William B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gillespie, G. W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gillespie, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Gillette, A. D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gillmore, Quincy A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gilman, Nicholas (Drawer Medium)
    - Gilmer, Jeremy Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Gilmer, Thomas W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gilmor, Harry (Drawer Medium)
    - Gilmor, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Gilprix, H. D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gilroy, Thomas F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Girard, Stephen (Drawer Medium)
    - Gist, States Rights (Drawer Medium)
    - Glaccum, John T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gladding, Munro H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gladstone, William Ewart, and Catherine (Drawer Medium)
    - Glasgow, Samuel L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Glazier, N. W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Glazier, Willard (Drawer Medium)
    - Glover, Thomas A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Goddard, Arabella (Drawer Medium)
    - Goddard, Calvin (Drawer Medium)
    - Goddard, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Godman, John D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Godwin, A. C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Godwin, Parke (Drawer Medium)
    - Goethe, Johann Wolfgang (Drawer Medium)
    - Goldberg, Arthur (Drawer Medium)
    - Goldsborough, Louis M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Goodrich, Chauncey (Drawer Medium)
    - Goodrich, Elizur (Drawer Medium)
    - Goodrich, John Yale (Drawer Medium)
    - Goodwin, Frederick Jordan CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Goodyear, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Gore, Christopher (Drawer Medium)
    - Gosman, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Gould (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Gould, George
      Gould, Hannah F.
      Gould, Jay